What am I sitting on?
내가 어디 앉아있지?
Top of the world?
세상의 꼭대기?
Dock of the bay?
해변의 항구?
난 빠질래
I'm out.
망측해라!
Oh, undies!
자, 누구 거야?
Whose are they?
-Whose are they?
-Not mine.
- 임자 나와
- 난 아냐
그럼 조이겠네 뭐
Joey's!
Got to be Joey's.
They're mine.
그래, 내 거야
봤지? 조이 맞잖아
See, Joey's.
They're Joe-Joe-Joey's.
- 왜 여기 있지?
- 글쎄...
Why are they here?
I don't know.
I'm Joey.
난 조이야
I'm disgusting.
메스꺼운 인간이지
남의 집에서 팬티나 벗고
I take my underwear off
in other people's homes.
Get them out of here.
What's wrong with you?
이거 갖고 나가
너 어디 아파?
- 그래
- 그럼
-Take them!
-I got them.
- 받아
- 알았어
얘, 만져도 돼
네 속옷이잖아
You can touch them.
They're yours.
Chandler? A word?
- 챈들러, 얘기 좀 할까?
- 네!
I'm tired of covering for you two.
This has got to stop.
됐어, 감싸주는 것도
하루 이틀이지, 그만해
꽉 쪼이는 흰 팬티?
너 8살이냐?
Tighty-whiteys?
What are you, 8?
Thank you, Joey, so much.
정말 고마워, 조이
됐어, 하나도 안 반가워
You're not welcome, okay?
나 정말 이거 싫다
계속 나만 얼굴 팔리잖아
Look, I hate this.
You guys keep embarrassing me.
Yesterday, Rachel found
your razor in our bathroom.
어젠 레이첼이 욕실에서
네 면도기를 봤어
그냥 내 거라도 둘러댔지 뭐
I said it was mine, and that
I was playing a woman in a play.
연극에서 여자 역을 맡았다고
거짓말을 하다 보니까...
Then one thing led
to another, and....
And around the ankles,
that is a tough spot.
발목 근처네
거기가 좀 힘들지
It was.
All right, listen
그렇더라, 잘 들어, 난...
거짓말하는 거 우리도 힘들어
All this lying has been
hard on us too.
그 많은 섹스로도
위로가 안 되든?
Yeah, I bet all the sex
makes it easier.
그렇긴 하지
Yeah, actually.
Meanwhile, I get Rachel shoving your
underwear in my face...
반면에 레이첼은 내 얼굴에
네놈 속옷을 들이밀면서
...and asking when she can
come see me star in Ugly Woman.
언제 '못난이 여인네'
공연하는 지나 묻고
앞으로는 조심할게
We'll be more careful.
We don't want them to know
because it's going really well.
들통나면 곤란해
지금 잘되고 있거든
And maybe it's going well
because it's a secret.
비밀에 부친 덕분에
잘되는 듯도 하고
이상하게 들리겠지만
우린 이런 관계에 서툴러
It sounds weird,
but we're so bad at relationships.
- 맞아, 도와줘
- 살려주라
-We are. Help us!
-Help!
All right.
But you do it with me once.
알았어, 하지만...
나랑 한 번 해야 돼
조이
-Joey!
-Didn't think so.
안 되겠지?
The One With Ross' Sandwich
-Can we please just drop this?
-But I don't get it.
이제 그만 좀 할래?
이해가 안 되잖아
덥다고 속옷까지 벗는
사람이 어디 있어?
Does anybody else just take off
their underwear when they're hot?
피비 왔니?
안녕, 피비
뭘 읽니?
What are you reading?
폭풍의 언덕
Wuthering Heights.
I have to finish it by tomorrow
for my literature class.
문학 강좌에 등록했는데
내일까지 다 읽어야 돼
그런 걸 들었니? 멋지다
You're taking a class?
That's so cool.
그래, 라마즈 강좌도
얼마나 좋았는데
I really liked
that Lamaze class I took.
이번엔 좀더 지적인 걸
듣고 싶어서
I thought this time I'd go
for something more intellectual...
...with a less painful final exam.
시험도 덜 힘들고
That sounds like fun.
재미있겠다
그럼, 너도 같이 가자
Oh, you should come with me!
와서 내 짝꿍 해라
Then I'll have someone to sit with.
그래
신난다, 근데 이거
읽을 시간 있니?
Do you have time to read it?
I read it in school.
고등학교 때 읽었어
This is going to be so much fun!
I have to finish.
정말 재미있겠다
시끄러, 책 좀 읽게
수업은 언제 시작...
But what time does the class start?
안녕?
그래
What's wrong, buddy?
왜 그러냐?
Someone at work ate my sandwich.
누가 내 샌드위치를 먹어버렸어
What did the police say?
경찰은 뭐라는데?
My Thanksgiving leftover sandwich.
추수감사절에 남은 건데
어떻게 그걸 손대냐고!
I can't believe someone ate it.
샌드위치 하나 갖고
뭘 그래?
It's just a sandwich.
Just a sandwich?
샌드위치 하나?
I am 30 years old, okay?
난 이제 서른인데 두 번이나
이혼하고 집에서 쫓겨났어
I'll be divorced twice and
I got evicted.
That sandwich was
the only good thing in my life!
그 샌드위치는 내 인생의
유일한 낙이었다고
Someone ate the only good thing
going on in my life!
내 인생의 유일한 낙을
누가 먹어버렸어
That's a nice sweater vest.
그 조끼 멋지다
샌드위치 하나
만들 재료는 있어
I have enough
for one more sandwich.
I was going to eat it myself, but....
내가 먹으려고 했지만...
Mon, that would be incredible.
Thank you so much.
이럴 수가, 정말 고맙다
그게 어떤 건데 먹어치워!
I still can't believe
someone ate it!
이걸 봐, 쪽지까지 남겼는데
Look, I left a note and everything.
똑똑, 누구세요?
로스 겔러의 점심
"Knock-knock."
"Who's there?"
"Ross Geller's lunch."
"Ross Geller's lunch, who?"
로스 겔러의 점심이라뇨?
"Ross Geller's lunch.
Please don't take me. Okay?"
로스 겔러의 점심이에요
날 먹지 마세요, 알았죠?
I'm surprised
you didn't wear it home.
넌 아까워서 먹지도 못하겠다
음식에 손을 못 대게
하려면 겁을 줘야 돼
Want to keep your food?
Scare people off.
거리에서 배운 거야
I learned that on the street.
정말?
Really?
What would you say, Phoebe?
넌 뭐라고 하는데?
Stuff like:
"Keep your mitts off my grub."
예를 들어...
'내 음식에 손대지 마! '
Do you picture Phoebe on the street
with the entire cast of Annie?
피비가 거리에서 '애니'
출연진들이랑 지냈을까?
이거면 확실하지
This'll keep them away
from your stuff.
Phoebe, you are a badass!
피비, 너 정말 못됐다
Someday I'll tell you
how I stabbed the cop.
나중에 내가 경찰
찌른 얘기 해줄게
- 피비
- 그 자식이 먼저 찔렀어!
He stabbed me first!
The Bronte sisters were remarkable women
for their time.
브론테 자매는 당대의
뛰어난 여성들이었어요
가부장적 사회에 살면서...
They lived in a patriarchal society.
Sorry I'm late,
but I left late.
늦어서 미안해
출발을 늦게 했거든
알았다
근데, 피비?
So, what is the book about?
책은 무슨 내용이야?
고등학교 때 읽었다며
Didn't you read it
in high school?
시작은 했는데 갑자기
집회가 있었던 것 같아
I started it, but then
there was this pep rally.
내 지위가 지위니 만큼
그건 그렇고...
And I was on top of the pyramid.
But anyway...
- 어떤 내용인데?
- 좋아
...what's the book about?
It's a tragic love story
between Cathy and Heathcliff.
캐시와 히스클리프의
비극적인 사랑 얘기야
배경은 영국의
황량한 광야인데
It takes place on these
creepy moors in England.
Which I think represent the wildness
of Heathcliff's character.
그 황야는 히스클리프의
성격을 대변하는 것 같아
I totally get symbolism.
상징주의가 별 거냐?
How would you characterize
the theme of this book?
이 작품의 주제를
설명해보겠어요?
어디 보자...
레이첼 그린
Let's see....
Rachel Greene?
I would have to say
that it's a tragic love story.
제 생각엔 비극적인
사랑 얘기 같군요
그건 잘 알려진
사실이지만 좋아요
That's sort of a given...
...but, yes.
Anyone else?
다른 사람?
오! 오! 오!
상징주의
Symbolism!
그리고 광야의 황량함은
And the wildness of the moors...
...which I think, is mirrored...
저의 견해로는 히스클리프의
거친 성격을 반영하고 있어요
...in the wildness
of Heathcliff's character.
Excellent! What Rachel
has shrewdly observed here....
훌륭합니다, 레이첼이
예리하게 간파했어요
내가 가르쳐줬잖아
You completely stole my answer!
Honey, that was pretty obvious.
뻔한 건데 뭐
How would you know?
You didn't read it!
읽지도 않았으면서
잘도 아는구나
어떻게 생각하세요
푸른색 셔츠 아가씨
What do you think?
You in the blue shirt?
I think that yours is a question
with many possible answers.
그 질문에는 여러 가지
대답이 나올 것 같군요
Would you care to venture one?
하나만 예를 들어볼까요?
하나만 예를 들어보시죠
Are you just repeating me?
내 말을 따라하는 겁니까?
제 말을 따라하는 거예요?
좋아요, 계속합시다
All right. Let's move on.
Okay, then.
그럼 됐어요
책 안 읽었다고 말하면 되잖아
Why didn't you say
you hadn't read the book?
I didn't want him
to think I was stupid.
거기서 바보 되란 말이야?
너도 얼마나 창피 당했니
That was really embarrassing,
what happened to you.
- 피비!
- 그래
Your note?
네가 적어준 거 끝내주더라
Amazing!
Not only did no one
touch my sandwich...
샌드위치 손댄 사람도 없지만
...but people at work are
actually afraid of me.
이젠 동료들이 날
무서워하는 거야
A guy called me "Mental."
어떤 사람은 나더러
'미치광이 겔러'라더라
"Mental Geller."
I've always wanted
a cool nickname like that.
드디어 멋진 별명이 생겼어
고교 때 제일 좋았던 게
'축축이 팬티 겔러'였거든
The best you got in high school
was "Wet Pants Geller."
분수식 음료수대 때문이었어!
It was the water fountain, okay?!
아무튼...
Anyway...
...people are writing
reports for me...
이제 날 위해 보고서도 올리고
내 일정에 시간을 맞추는 거야
...pushing back deadlines
to fit my schedule.
I tell you,
you get tough with people...
상대를 거칠게 다뤄야
원하는 걸 얻을 수 있어
...and you can get
anything you want.
임마, 트리비아니
당장 그 커피 내놔
Hey, Tribbiani!
Give me that coffee! Now!
This was really fun.
정말 재미있었어요
I've been wondering
if you'd ask me out.
데이트 신청
안 할 줄 알았는데
So you still wondering?
아직도 그렇게 생각해요?
아니, 방금 데이트했잖아요
No. We just went out.
You're smart.
똑똑하군요
맘에 들어요
I like that.
Oh, candles!
촛불이다
What is that, a blanket?
이건 뭐죠? 담요?
A video camera?
Oh, my God!
비디오카메라까지...
세상에!
그게 아니라...
I can't believe you thought you'd
tape us having sex on the first date!
첫 데이트에 섹스 장면을
녹화하겠다니 제정신이에요?
왔니?
Joey, is what she just said....
조이, 방금 저 여자가...
Oh, my God!
맙소사, 너 진짜로...
You're actually going
What is going on here?
이게 무슨 일이지?
And with Chandler in the next room.
What are you, sick?
챈들러도 옆방에 있는데
너 어디 아파?
I'm Joey.
난 조이란다
I mean, I'm disgusting.
메스꺼운 인간이야
I make low-budget adult films.
저 예산 성인영화를 만들어
You promised to be more careful!
조심한다고 약속했잖아
The good Joey name's been
dragged through the mud!
드높던 조이의 명예가
진창에 굴러 떨어졌어
We're so sorry.
- 미안해
- 그래
I'm telling everyone.
다 불어버릴 테야
It's the only explanation that
doesn't make me look like a pig!
속옷이랑 비디오테이프 사건을
해명하고 돼지 신세 면하겠어
No, there's a better explanation.
달리 해명하면 되잖아
성인영화를 만든 건..
Tell them you had to make
an adult film for your...
성인영화강좌 때문이라고
...adult film class.
I like that.
But no!
그건 좋다만, 아니지
How does that explain
my underwear at your place?
너희 집에서 내 속옷이
나온 건 어떻게 설명할래
I don't know.
모르겠다
이제 게이가 아닌 걸
떳떳하게 밝히시지
Get ready to come out
of the non-gay closet.
I promise to come up with something.
Just give us time.
좋은 방법을 생각해볼게
조금만 시간을 줘
All right.
알았어
But it better make me
look really good.
내 체면 확실히 살려놔야 돼
And another thing:
하나 더
The video camera?
비디오카메라?
제법이다
Nice!
선사시대 박물관
로스
May I have a word?
얘기 좀 해도 될까?
물론이죠
Of course, Donald.
We've been getting reports
of very angry behavior on your part.
자네한테 문제가 있다는
보고서가 올라오는데
- 네?
- 협박편지와 업무일정 지연
-What?
-Threatening letters...
...refusal to meet deadlines.
Apparently people now
call you Mental.
이제 동료들 사이에서
미치광이로 통한다고?
네
We want you to speak
to a psychiatrist.
정신과에 한번 가보게
아뇨...
You don't understand.
This is so silly.
잘 모르시나 본데
창피한 얘기지만
This is all just
because of a sandwich.
이건 모두 샌드위치
하나 때문에 생긴 일입니다
A sandwich?
샌드위치?
네, 제 여동생이 기가 막힌
칠면조 샌드위치를 만드는데
You see, my sister makes
these amazing turkey sandwiches.
Her secret is, she puts an extra slice
of gravy-soaked bread in the middle.
맛의 비결은 육수에 절인
빵을 중간에 넣은 겁니다
I call it "The Moistmaker."
전 그걸 '보습제'라고 하죠
Anyway, I put my sandwich
in the fridge....
어쨌든 저는 샌드위치를
이 냉장고에 넣어두는데...
Oh, you know what?
- 이걸 어쩌나...
- 뭘요?
I'm sorry.
미안하네...
내가 먹었어
I believe I ate that.
You ate my sandwich?
제 샌드위치를 드셨어요?
A simple mistake.
It can happen to anyone.
누구나 할 수 있는 실수 아닌가
그런 가요?
Oh, really?
Did you confuse it with your own
turkey sandwich with a Moistmaker?
요즘은 보습제로 무장한 칠면조
샌드위치가 흔한가 보죠?
아니...
Do you, perhaps, remember...
혹시 그 위에 쪽지가
한 장 있지 않던가요?
...seeing a note on top of it?
There may have been a joke
or limerick of some kind.
무슨 농담이나...
5행시였던가?
제 샌드위치라고
적혀 있었습니다
That said it was...
...my sandwich!
Now, calm down.
진정하게
Look in my office.
Some may be in the trash.
내 방으로 가세
남은 게 휴지통에 있을 거야
네?
It was quite large.
I had to throw most of it away.
너무 커서
다 먹을 수가 없었어
그니까 내 샌드위치를
버렸다 이 겁니까?
You threw my sandwich away?
내 샌드위치를?
My sandwich?!
내 샌드위치를!
- 나 왔어
- 그래
What's this book about?
- 이 책은 또 뭔데?
- 이것도 안 읽었어?
You didn't read it, either?
읽으려고 했는데
다른 책이 보여서
I was going to, but I accidentally
read something else.
- 뭔데?
- 보그
Vogue.
So tell me about Jane Eyre.
제인 에어에 대해 설명해봐
No, read it yourself.
네가 직접 읽어라
범생이처럼 그럴 거 없잖아
Come on,
don't be such a goody-goody.
Fine.
좋아
- 알았어, 제인 에어는
- 그래
All right.
So, Jane Eyre?
First, you'd think she's a woman,
but she's not.
여자인 줄 알겠지만
놀랍게도 사이보그야
She's a cyborg.
A cyborg?
Isn't that like a robot?
사이보그라면
로봇 같은 거지?
This book was light years
ahead of its time.
몇 광년 미래의 얘기거든
Sorry I'm late.
Let's get started.
늦어서 미안합니다
빨리 시작하죠
다들 제인 에어에 대해
어떻게 생각하세요
What did you think of Jane Eyre?
Rachel and I were discussing it,
and she had very interesting insights.
방금 레이첼이랑 얘기했는데
흥미로운 의견이 있더군요
Go ahead, Rachel.
그럼 들어볼까요, 레이첼?
Thank you, Phoebe.
고맙다, 피비
제인 에어에서 가장
인상 깊었던 점은
What struck me most
when reading Jane Eyre...
시대를 앞서간다는 거였어요
...was how the book was
so ahead of its time.
If you're talking about feminism,
I think you're right.
페미니즘을 말하는 거라면
제대로 봤어요
네, 페미니즘도 그렇지만
로봇도 빠질 수 없죠
Well, feminism, yes.
But also the robots.
- 왔어?
- 그래
저기... 비디오카메라는
실패했잖아?
Since that video camera thing
didn't work out...
...I thought that I would give you
just a little preview.
그래서 예고편을 잠깐
보여줄까 하고
You're naked!
다 벗었잖아
I know!
알아
오빠야
로스?
안녕, 챈들러?
모니카!
Are you okay?
오빠 괜찮아?
I'm fine.
그럼, 오늘 직장에서
정신과의사를 만났어
I saw a psychiatrist at work today.
Why?
- 왜?
- 내 분노 때문에
On account of my rage.
Which, if I may say,
right now is out of control.
이제 완전 고삐가 풀린 거야?
He gave me a pill for it.
약을 주더라
A pill?
약?
When the psychiatrist told me
to take a leave of absence...
상사한테 소리 좀 질렀다고
정신과의사가 휴직하라길래
...because I yelled at my boss,
I started to get worked up again.
또 화를 냈더니
진정제를 주는 거야
So he offered me a tranquilizer.
And I thought it was a good idea.
좋은 생각 같더라
So I took it.
그래서 먹었지
They're making you take
time off work?
잠깐, 강제로 휴직을 시켰어?
And you're okay with that?
- 그래도 괜찮아?
- 몰라
I don't know.
It's going to be weird
not having a job for a while.
뜻하지 않게 잠시 백수가 됐지만
But I definitely don't care
about my sandwich.
이제 샌드위치 걱정은 안 해
I hate it when they make me see
the shrink at my office.
나도 직장에서 정신과
상담을 받으면 꼭 이래
He's always like, "Your colleagues will
like you better if you like yourself better."
'동료들의 사랑을 받으려면
자기 자신부터 사랑하세요'
Who needs that?
쓰잘데 없이...
-You do.
-I know.
- 맞는 말이네
- 알아
It's so embarrassing! I can't believe
you let me go on like that!
낮 뜨거워서, 넌 어떻게
옆에서 구경만 할 수 있니
I'm sorry.
미안하다
It was so funny when you compared
Jane Eyre to Robocop.
제인 에어랑 로보캅을
비교하니까 참 웃기더라
That was not funny!
난 하나도 안 웃겨
I snapped, okay?
You weren't taking the class seriously.
강의를 장난으로 생각하니까
정신 좀 차리라고 그런 거야
Come on!
What is the big deal?
넌 뭐가 그렇게 심각해?
I thought it'd be something
we could do together.
함께 어울리면서
재미있으면 됐잖아
I thought it would be fun.
Fun is good.
재미도 좋지만
난 뭔가 배우고 싶어
But I also wanted to learn.
People talk about what they learned
in high school. I never went.
난 남들처럼 고등학교도
제대로 못 나왔잖아
So you really wanted to learn.
그래서 정말 배우고 싶었구나
You know, Phoebe,
I just wanted to have fun.
난 그냥 놀 생각만 했네
You know who should go?
같이 갈 사람 있다
I know! I know! I know!
저요! 저요! 저요!
Monica, you asked the question.
모니카가 질문한 거잖아요
Oh, my God, that's Monica!
엄마야, 모니카잖아!
아냐, 아냐, 아냐...
가까이 오지 마
구제불능 변태야
You get away from me,
you sick, sick, sicko!
What's going on?
왜 그래?
조이가 몰래 훔쳐보는
구멍이 있어
Joey has got a secret peephole!
-Oh, no!
-Yes, he has a naked picture of Monica!
안 돼, 안 돼, 안 돼
그래, 모니카 알몸을 찍고
우리 알몸도 찍고
He takes naked pictures of us, then
he eats chicken and looks at them!
치킨 먹으면서
그걸 보고 있어
- 봐!
- 치워, 내 동생이야
Oh! Dude, that's my sister!
Give me that!
이리 줘
다들 잠깐만 진정해
Wait! Everybody calm down, okay?
변명할 기회를 주자
왕 변태 녀석한테!
Let's give our friend a chance
to explain why he's such a big pervert!
난 절대 변태가 아냐
그냥...
I am not a pervert, okay?
It's just....
I just kind of....
- 그게 뭐시기냐...
- 잠깐
I think I can explain this.
됐어, 내가 설명할게
Thank you.
고맙다
Joey's a sex addict.
조이는 섹스중독자야
What?! No, I'm not!
뭐? 아냐
It's okay! It's good!
괜찮아, 오히려 잘된 거야
It's a disease.
이건 질병이니까
- 아냐, 누구더러 섹스중독자래
- 맞아
I am not a sex addict!
Yes, you are!
That's the only way
to explain all this stuff!
모든 게 설명되잖아
No, it isn't. It's not.
아니, 그렇지 않아
너희가 진실을 밝혀야 설명이 돼
Because you could also explain it
with the truth!
What is the truth?
진실이 뭔데?
-What's up?
-What's going on?
- 그래, 뭐야?
- 무슨 일인데?
I slept with Monica.
내가 모니카랑 잤어
Well, let's see what everybody
thinks of that.
다들 어떻게 생각하나 볼까?
안 돼...
You slept with my sister?
내 동생이랑 잤어?
그래, 하지만 런던에서
딱 한 번이야
Yes, but it was
We just did it once, in London.
This is not good for my rage.
내 상태가 더 악화되겠다
모니카?
Is this true?
- 정말이니?
- 물론이지
Of course, it's true.
How else would you explain all the
weird stuff that's been going on?
아니면 요즘의 괴변들을
설명할 방법이 없지
Yes, it's true.
그래, 사실이야
한 번인데 왜 네 속옷이
우리 아파트에서 나오니?
If it happened once, how come we
found your underwear in our apartment?
그거?
That was the underwear
I was wearing that night in London.
그게 바로 런던에서
입었던 속옷이야
Right, Monica?
안 그래, 모니카?
I guess I wanted to keep it...
간직하고 싶었어
...as a souvenir.
기념품으로
My God, Monica!
세상에, 모니카
Are you sure you're not
just a sex addict?
진짜야, 조이?
너 섹스중독 아냐?
아냐
여기 섹스중독자가 있다면
그건 모니카야
If anyone's a sex addict here,
it's Monica.
아무렴
She has been trying to get me back
in the sack ever since London!
그 이후로 틈만 나면 날
침대로 끌어들이려 했어
That's why she gave you
a naked picture of herself.
그래서 알몸 사진을 줬구나
That makes sense.
일리가 있네
And the video camera?
비디오카메라도?
모니카?
I guess I set up the video camera
to try and entice Joey.
조이를 유혹하려고
카메라를 설치했어
But, sadly, I could not be enticed.
하지만 슬프게도
유혹에 안 넘어갔지
모니카, 당장 그만둬라
Monica, this has to stop now.
I know, I know.
나도 알아, 안다고
그러고 싶어
I know. I will, and I would appreciate
if we all could just...
모두 없었던 일로
덮어줬으면 좋겠어
...drop it immediately, and forever.
영원히
Okay. That is, if you can resist me.
좋아, 날 거부할 수 있다면
-I'll give it my best shot.
-Good luck.
- 최선을 다해볼게
- 행운이 있기를!
Unbelievable!
세상에, 진짜로 조이의
속옷을 간직하려 했니?
You really kept Joey's underwear?
Why? Why would you do that?
도대체 왜 그랬어?
I'm Monica.
난 모니카야
I'm disgusting.
메스꺼운 인간이지
I stalk guys and keep their underpants.
남자들 따라다니며
팬티를 수집해
좋아
I think we've all learned
who's disgusting and who's not.
이제 진짜 메스꺼운 사람을
찾은 것 같군, 에?
좋았어, 난 이제
본업으로 돌아가련다
Now, I'm going to get back
to my bucket.
I'm only eating the skin,
so the chicken's up for grabs.
껍질만 먹어서 알맹이는
멀쩡한데 먹을래?
You were making a good point.
핵심을 지적한 것 같아요
중간에 끊겼지만...
I mean, till you got cut off.
What's up with that girl Monica?
모니카란 여자는 왜 그런대요?
I don't know.
I didn't come with her.
몰라요, 같이 안 왔어요
여러분, 기대하세요
Hey, everybody!
Everybody, guess what!
I just convinced Carl
to give us a test.
다음주에 시험 보자고 했어요
Test?
시험?
Come on!
Tests make us all better learners!
시험을 보면 실력이 향상되잖아요
Oh, yeah!
We should have essay questions!
그래, 에세이도 넣어야겠다!